glowpink.com 2016-11-23

# Glowpink

Your privacy is important to us and, to better protect it, we have we provided you with an explanation of our Privacy Policy below. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, we kindly ask you to leave the site.

  1. Do not disclose any personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name, email address, phone number, and date of birth in any section of the website, irrespective of whether you have paid for the service or not. The information you submit to Glowpink may be used to help other users who are searching for information about similar health conditions. Any information that you submit to Glowpink is searchable by search engines.
  2. The information you submit to Glowpink may be seen by service providers, such as doctors, or by operations and maintenance teams repairing and maintaining our technical systems. Glowpink does not have Non-Disclosure Agreements with these parties, who may be able to access your information.
  3. Glowpink may use the information you submit to Glowpink to study results and produce reports. Such information may be shared with Glowpink partners and advertisers under the sole discretion of Glowpink.
  4. In the case of danger to self or others, and in the case of any legal investigation, Glowpink has the right to share your information with the law enforcement authorities.
  5. Glowpink's websites contain links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website collecting personal information.
  6. We will send emails to the email address you provide, and we will call the phone numbers you provide, if required. In case you have given a wrong email address or phone number for correspondence, Glowpink is not responsible for any loss of information or privacy. 
  7. Glowpink uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. 
  8. Third-party vendors, including Google, show Glowpink's ads on sites across the Internet. 
  9. Glowpink and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and deliver ads based on someone's past visits to our website. 

**Your use of the site, the services and the content is subject to the above Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Fair Usage Policy and Disclaimer. If you find these Conditions unacceptable, we request that you do not use this portal.**

...
